<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CCENT Quiz</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="activity_start_button">Start Quiz!</string>
    <string name="title_screen_text">CCENT Quiz!</string>


    <string-array name="one_questions_array">

        <item>A fellow engineer tells you to configure the DHCP server to lease the last 100
            usable IP addresses in subnet 10.1.4.0/23. Which of the following IP addresses
            could be leased as a result of your new configurations?\n\n
            a. 10.1.4.156\n
            b. 10.1.4.254\n
            c. 10.1.5.200\n
            d. 10.1.7.200
        </item>
        <item>An enterprise puts the DHCP and DNS servers on VLAN 10/subnet 10 in Atlanta,
            using IP address 10.1.10.1 for the DHCP server and 10.1.10.2 for the DNS server.
            A remote router sits in Boston, with devices on the Boston LAN using the DHCP and DNS
            servers in Atlanta. Which of the followingneeds to be configured in the routers
            in this enterprise to support DHCP and DNS?\n\n
            a. The \"ip helper-address 10.1.10.1\" command in the Atlanta router\n
            b. The \"ip helper-address 10.1.10.2\" command in the Boston router\n
            c. The \"ip name-server 10.1.10.2\" command in the Atlanta router\n
            d. none of the above
        </item>
        <item>R4 has a connected route for 172.16.8.0/22. Which of the following answers
            list a subnet that overlaps with this subnet?\n\n
            a. 172.16.0.0/21\n
            b. 172.16.11.0/25\n
            c. 172.16.6.0/23\n
            d. 172.16.16.0/20
        </item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="multi_questions_array">

        <item>Each answer lists two types of devices used in a 100BASE-T network.
            If these devices were connected with UTP Ethernet cables, which pairs
            of devices would require a straight-through cable? \n\n
            a. PC and router\n
            b. PC and switch\n
            c. Wireless access point and switch\n
            d. Router and hub
        </item>
        <item>An engineer had formerly configured a Cisco 2960 switch to allow Telnet access so
            that the switch expected a password of \"mypassword\" from the Telnet user. The engineer
            then changed the configuration to support Secure Shell. Which of the following commands
            could have been part of the new configuration?\n\n
            a. A \"username [name] password [password]\"  vty mode subcommand\n
            b. A \"username [name] password [password]\"  global config command\n
            c. A \"login local\"  vty mode subcommand\n
            d. A \"transport input ssh\"  global config command
        </item>
        <item>Which of the following are true about IP address 172.16.99.45\'s IP network?\n\n
            a. The network ID is 172.0.0.0\n
            b. The network is a Class B network\n
            c. The default mask for the network is 255.255.255.0\n
            d. The number of host bits in the unsubnetted network is 16
        </item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="open_questions_array">

        <item>What does OSPF stand for?
        </item>
        <item>What is the command that lists a summary of the LSAs in the local router\'s
        LSDB, listing one line for each LSA?
        </item>
        <item>What is the command that Lists one line per interface on which OSPF is enabled,
            for all interfaces (including passive interfaces) on which OSPF is enabled?.
        </item>

    </string-array>
</resources>
